# **Andrew Popp**

Email: apopp524@gmail.com Tel: (314) 347-5558 | Location: Skyline Dr, KS, 66205

LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/30O8m4q | GitHub:https://bit.ly/2DXbou1

Portfolio: https://bit.ly/3gISsO1

Full Stack Web Developer with a Digital Media Production degree and experience in the live events, media, and television industry. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack development from the University of Kansas with new skills in JavaScript, jQuery, CSS3, HTML5, MySQL, NoSQL, Node.js, React.js and responsive web design. Self-motivated problem solver that is flexible working with a team or individually and always striving to learn and find new creative challenges everyday.

#### **Technical Skills**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, MySQL, NoSQL, Heroku, Bootstrap, Bulma, GIT, GitHub, Adobe Creative Suite

# **Projects**

- Exploration Food Selective Recipe App designed to match the needs of all diets and food restrictions. Great for those with allergies, religious restrictions, or are simply particular about their food.
- As a Front-End Developer on this project I worked on the wireframing, overall layout and functionality of the website.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bulma

- Simply type in a city around the world in the search bar and the Weather Dashboard will come up with the current and future weather information.
- Working on the Front and Back end of this project required a simple Bootstrap layout and incorporating the API with iOuery.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, Bootstrap, OpenWeatherMap API

Day Planner | Link to Github: <a href="https://bit.ly/3agYBPi">https://bit.ly/3agYMdq</a> | Link to Deployed Project: <a href="https://bit.ly/3agYMdq">https://bit.ly/3agYMdq</a> | Full-Stack Developer

- This planner application will allow you to schedule events for any 9am-5pm work day.
- This application was put together using HTML and CSS and runs smoothly with jQuery.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, Bootstrap

## **Experience**

May 2018 - March 2020

#### Harvest Productions, North Kansas City, MO - Lead Video Technician

- Lead video for live event productions such as conferences, expos, concerts, sporting events, and shows.
- Communicated with clients for Audio and Visual troubleshooting, maintenance, and content creation.

April 2019 - January 2020

## Major League Baseball, Kansas City, MO - Data Operations

- Video Room Monitor for home and away teams during Royals games at Kauffman Stadium.
- Statistical tracking during Royals games.

January 2016 - January 2018

## KMOS-TV, Warrensburg, MO - Producer

- Television studio production, filming, and editing for shows *Pause, Show-Me Ag, Lowdown*
- Live television filming and replay for University of Central Missouri sporting events.

### Education

- University of Kansas BootCamp Full Stack Web Development, Lawrence, KS
  - An intensive 6 month long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications. Skills learned consisted of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js
- Bachelor of Science Digital Media Production degree, University of Central Missouri, Warrensburg, MO
  - Graduated May 2018 with a minor in Sports Communication and specialized coursework in Video & Audio Production, Media Promotions, Digital Video Editing, HTML & CSS Basics